{
    "id": "7daad3ef116e4f41962f80150ce3ec45",
    "title": "Phrasal Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. his hard work, he failed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By means of",
                "In spite of",
                "Because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72c622b0548c4fb8be0a79af2043d57f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… doctors, smoking can cause cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In accordance with",
                "According to",
                "On behalf of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8cdf9aa904014532935e0ca1e4c35150"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am standing here ………………… my colleagues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead of",
                "by means of",
                "on behalf of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0446f366a77b4c129aadb015676ec825"
        },
        {
            "question": "The trains arrived late ……………….. heavy rains.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in spite of",
                "on behalf of",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40ffd1060a6f4e829588f1bc083e4daa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed in bed all day ……………… going to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in addition to",
                "in spite of",
                "instead of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af59d7c9b94d4686af4e868681bf9424"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thoughts are conveyed ………………… words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on account of",
                "by means of",
                "by virtue of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f447f887d104c0485ccf937f7c819a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gandhi gave up his legal practice ………………… his country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by virtue of",
                "for the sake of",
                "on behalf of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a3d38e2410f48a89117c11ed339637e"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. his own family, he has to support his brother’s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In addition to",
                "Instead of",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35e26903807b4040870b088aaa67c271"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a school …………………. my house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "front of",
                "in front of",
                "in front"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71a27fa6fa994c2b93478a681325f3d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to have lemon juice ………………… coffee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead",
                "instead of",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bdbaaa8ec80f4569a2ecf4aa5ea686e5"
        }
    ]
}